var questions= [{
    id:1,
    question:'RQP, ONM, LKJ, _____, FED',
    option1:'IHG',
    option2:'CAB',
    option3:'JKL',
    option4:'GHI',
    answer:'1',
},{
    id:2,
    question:'KBJ, LCK, MDL, NEM, _____',
    option1:'OEP',
    option2:'OFN',
    option3:'MEN',
    option4:'PFQ',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:3,
    question:'Find the next number in the sequence: 3, 6, 9, 30, 117...... ',
    option1:'192',
    option2:'352',
    option3:'388',
    option4:'588',
    answer:'D',
    
},{
    id:4,
    question:'Find the next number in the sequence: 26, 63, 124, 215, 342..... ',
    option1:'416',
    option2:'511',
    option3:'686',
    option4:'559',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:5,
    question:'Find the next number in the sequence: 104, 109, 115, 122, 130..... ',
    option1:'119',
    option2:'125',
    option3:'139',
    option4:'134',
    answer:'3',
},{
    id:6,
    question:'DEF, DEF2, DE2F2, _____, D2E2F3',
    option1:'DEF3',
    option2:'D3EF3',
    option3:'D2E3F',
    option4:'D2E2F2',
    answer:'4',
},{
    id:7,
    question:'QAR, RAS, SAT, TAU, _____',
    option1:'UAV',
    option2:'UAT',
    option3:'TAS',
    option4:'TAT',
    answer:'1',
},{
    id:8,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'tulip',
    option2:'rose',
    option3:'bud',
    option4:'daisy',
    answer:'3',
},{
    id:9,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'inch',
    option2:'ounce',
    option3:'centimeter',
    option4:'yard',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:10,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'cornea',
    option2:'retina',
    option3:'pupil',
    option4:'vision',
    answer:'4',
},{
    id:11,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'core',
    option2:'seeds',
    option3:'pulp',
    option4:'slice',
    answer:'4',
},{
    id:12,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'biology',
    option2:'chemistry',
    option3:'theology',
    option4:'zoology',
    answer:'3',
},{
    id:13,
    question:'Which word does NOT belong with the others?',
    option1:'eel',
    option2:'lobster',
    option3:'crab',
    option4:'shrimp',
    answer:'1',
},{
    id:14,
    question:'Look at this series: V, VIII, XI, XIV, __, XX, ... What number should fill the blank?',
    option1:'IX',
    option2:'XXIII',
    option3:'XV',
    option4:'XVII',
    answer:'4',
},{
    id:15,
    question:'Look at this series: J14, L16, __, P20, R22, ... What number should fill the blank?',
    option1:'S24',
    option2:'N18',
    option3:'M18',
    option4:'T24',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:16,
    question:'Look at this series: VI, 10, V, 11, __, 12, III, ... What number should fill the blank?',
    option1:'II',
    option2:'IV',
    option3:'IX',
    option4:'14',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:17,
    question:'Look at this series: (1/9), (1/3), 1, ____ , 9, ... What number should fill the blank?',
    option1:'(2/3)',
    option2:'3',
    option3:'6',
    option4:'27',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:18,
    question:'Look carefully for the pattern, and then choose which pair of numbers comes next. 6 10 14 18 22 26 30 ..., ... ',
    option1:'36 40',
    option2:'33 37',
    option3:'38 42',
    option4:'34 38',
    answer:'4',
},{
    id:19,
    question:'Cup is to coffee as bowl is to',
    option1:'dish',
    option2:'soup',
    option3:'spoon',
    option4:'food',
    answer:'2',
},{
    id:20,
    question:'Optimist is to cheerful as pessimist is to',
    option1:'gloomy',
    option2:'mean',
    option3:'petty',
    option4:'helpful',
    answer:'1',
},{
    id:21,
    question:'Exercise is to gym as eating is to',
    option1:'food',
    option2:'dieting',
    option3:'fitness',
    option4:'restaurant',
    answer:'4',
}]